Yeah, I am the astro creep
A demolition style
Hell american freak, yeah
I am the crawling dead
A phantom in a box
Shadow in your head say
Acid, suicide freedom of the blast
Read the fucker lies, yeah
Scratch off the broken skin
Tear into my heart make
Me do it again yeah
Yeah [x4]

More Human Than Human
[x6]

Yeah, I am the jigsaw man
I turn the world around
With a skeleton hand say
I am electric head
A cannibal core
A television said, yeah
Do not victimize
Read the motherfucker
Psychoholic lies, yeah
Into a psychic war
I tear my soul apart and I
Eat it some more, yeah
Yeah [x4]

More Human Than Human
[x6]

Yeah, I am the ripper man
A locomotion mind
Love american style, yeah
I am the nexus one
I want more life fucker
I ain't done, yeah

More Human Than Human
[x8]